

CONTACT



Email

jelenasuvajac.design@gmail.com



LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/suvajacjelena



Web-Page

https://jelena-suvajac.netlify.app



Address

Novi Sad, Serbia



- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe XD
- Adobe InDesing
- Figma



LANGUAGE

- English- Professional working proficiency
- Serbian- Native or bilingual proficiency

JELENA SUVAJAC

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | UX/UI DESIGNER



PROFILE

I'm Jelena Suvajac, a junior Graphic designer with several years of experience in the industry.

Throughout my career, I have developed a diverse set of skills that encompass reliability, creativity, ambition, and dedication to teamwork. I approach each task with responsibility and a sincere desire for continuous improvement. I deeply believe in the power of learning and actively seek opportunities to expand my knowledge and expertise, while demonstrating a high level of adaptability in various situations.



WORKING EXPERIENCE

\triangleright	Graphic Designer	2016 - 2023
	Freelance	

Fitness Instructor 2011 - 2019 Karanovic Gym (Part - Time)

2019 **Production Operator** Lear Corporation, Novi Sad

2011 - 2013 \sim **Children Animator** Castello Playroom, Novi Sad



EDUCATION

- 2023 **Graphic Designer** FTN-Informatika d.o.o.
- 2006 2010 **Veterinary Technician** Agricultural High School, Novi Sad